

### **About Me**

I am a Computer Science graduate from Curtin University Dubai. My academic and professional experience has allowed me to develop skills in various fields such as Web/App Research and Development (UI/UX - Frontend development, Backend development), Design (Graphic Design, Basic 3D Modelling), and Digital Marketing (Social Media). I am keen to explore the frontend design and development space more through opportunities that will enable me to use my skills and further grow them within a professional environment.

### Skills

- Web Design
- Ability to work under pressure
- Communication Skills
- Leadership
- Effective Time Management
- Critical thinking and problem-solving
- Fast Learner

### Languages

English - (Fluent)

Arabic - (Native Language)

## **Nationality**

Antigua and Barbuda (Valid Resident in Qatar)

# **OMAR ATAYA**

**Phone** +974 7044 3379

Email omar\_ataya@outlook.com

Address
The Pearl, Doha

## **Experience**

#### Web Developer

2022 - Current

### Bianca-nera, Doha

As a Full Stack Web Developer at Bianca-nera my roles included working on a store management website where tasks done by the employees are logged and can be tracked by the store managers

#### Founder

2020 - Current

#### Neonwave, Dubai

NeonWave is a neon signs business I started during Covid as a side project, I handle all the day-to-day operations from contacting suppliers and couriers, managing stocks, dealing with customers and following up with all parties as well as managing the business's website, social media and the marketing of it.

- Organically grew the Instagram account followers count to 7K
- Collaborated with high profile international influencers in the MENA region

### App Research and Development Intern Amalthea Captial Limited, Dubai

2021 - 2022

I was part of a team consisting of 4 members on a Fin-tech Education app development project, the first stage of the internship was understanding and researching the fin-tech app market and competitions in the education category, the next stage was creating different app concept designs(UX/UI) and the last stage was the app development stage using android studio, java and dart(flutter) where I assisted in the front-end design and development of the app as well as designing the project website using HTML, CSS and JS.

### **Education**

## Bachelor of Science (Information Technology)

2018 - 2022

#### Curtin University, Dubai

A fresh graduate with Distinction, pursuing a Bachelor's degree in Computer Science. 3.67 GPA (Australian weight)

## **Projects**

#### PAAT

#### Curtin University, Dubai

Packet Amplification Assessment Tool is the graduation project I worked on with a group 4 other students, the goal of the project is creating a software to prevent NTP, SSDP and DNS amplification attacks by sending packets and checking if the response is amplified. I was part of the frontend developing team where I worked on the project's frontend using python language utilizing libraries such as pyqt5.

#### Textilreinigung Malah Website

Doha

Developed and hosted an informational website for a laundry shop located in Vienna, it included the services they provided along with the prices for those services. Technologies:

Next Js - Netlify - HTML & CSS3(Bootstrap & Tailwind)

Link: textilreinigung-malah.com